<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hacking on santricyber</title>
    <link>https://www.santricyber.com/categories/hacking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hacking on santricyber</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:55:44 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.santricyber.com/categories/hacking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Penetration Testing Note for Me</title>
      <link>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/pentest-guide-for-beginner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:55:44 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/pentest-guide-for-beginner/</guid>
      <description>Pada kesempatan yang baik ini saya ingin mencatat hal-hal yang akan saya pelajari dan saya dokumentasikan ke dalam Blog ini terkait course yang akan saya jalani mulai 17 juni 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Tracking IP Address With Ping and Nslookup</title>
      <link>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:33:59 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</guid>
      <description>Like the part that I previously explained in hacking activities is information gathering, while in information gathering things that are usually collected include IP Address username email address operating system if what we are targeting is a website, of course, we also have to know what technology is used on our target website, both the programming language used, the database used.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create an IP Checker Tool in Python</title>
      <link>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:28:03 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</guid>
      <description>At this stage of the ethical hacking series, I will share the source code for how to make the IP Checker tool using the Python programming language on our Kali Linux operating system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethical Hacking Part 1 Information Gathring</title>
      <link>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 11:10:50 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</guid>
      <description>It should be remembered that this article is a series of lessons from part 1 on ethical hacking to part 7 that I studied, to summarize so that there is not too much discussion I decided to shorten the discussion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Recon for Cyber Warriors</title>
      <link>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 06:47:43 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.santricyber.com/posts/2024/information-gathring/</guid>
      <description>IMPORTANT! Notes on ethical hacking series I am not a hacker!,&amp;hellip;&#xA;although in this series there is a discussion about hacking but hacking in the sense of ethical hacking to build awareness of the security side in cyberspace and learning, the writings that I make are purely as a record of the results of my knowledge and in share for purposes that I hope will be useful to anyone who reads it with good intentions including increasing awareness of security in cyberspace and overcoming losses due to cybercrime.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
